{
    "subject": "resource/Mechel_Scheuer",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Frankfurt_am_Main",
    "human_readable": "Mechel Scheuer was born in Frankfurt am Main.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9707848429679871,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Frankfurt am Main when Mechel Scheuer was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8697049617767334,
            "question": "Where was Mechel Scheuer born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.782326877117157,
            "question": "What year was Mechel Scheuer born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6921378970146179,
            "question": "What is the significance of being born in Frankfurt am Main?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5225080251693726,
            "question": "What is Mechel Scheuer known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48367542028427124,
            "question": "What is Frankfurt am Main known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4269659221172333,
            "question": "Is Mechel Scheuer related to any famous people?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4173455834388733,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Mechel Scheuer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3738917112350464,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Mechel Scheuer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29675009846687317,
            "question": "Do you know any stories about Mechel Scheuer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mechel Scheuer was born in Frankfurt am Main.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4014_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Mechel Scheuer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4014_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information available about Mechel Scheuer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4014_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mechel Scheuer related to any famous people?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4014_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4014_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Abraham Naftali Hertz Scheuer and his brother Rabbi Mechel Scheuer,  they don't state where Rabbi Mechel Scheuer was born. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThere is no mention of Mechel Scheuer's birthplace in the documents. In fact, one document mentions a different person named Abraham Naftali Hertz Scheuer who was born in Frankfurt am Main."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information provided does not mention anything about Mechel Scheuer being born in Frankfurt am Main. Instead, the documents discuss Abraham Naftali Hertz Scheuer and Michel Scheuer, neither of whom is mentioned as being born in Frankfurt am Main."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Mechel Scheuer is not explicitly mentioned in the context information provided.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Michel Scheuer's information states he was born in Rodange, Luxembourg.  Since Mechel Scheuer led the yeshiva in Mainz and became Rabbi of Mainz it is unlikely he would be born in Frankfurt am Main.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information suggesting Mechel Scheuer was born in Frankfurt am Main, but rather that Abraham Naftali Hertz Scheuer and his son Rabbi David Tebele Scheuer were.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Michel Scheuer was born in Rodange, Luxembourg, not Frankfurt am Main.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}